

Rosario, Santa Fe - Argentina.

maxidelfino1234@hotmail.com

+54 9 341 321-1539

www.MaxDesing.com

Availability: Part time





About me

Hi, I introduce myself! I'm 23 years old, and I'm a Software Developer, currently focused on website development.

I'm fascinated by the world of technology and since then my goal is to grow as a professional by constantly acquiring tools in the area.

I have experience with the MERN stack (Mongo DB, Express Js, React Js, Node Js).

Besides being a systems engineering student at the Universidad Tecnológica Nacional of Rosario.

Skills

Clean code writing, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Curious, Versatile, Good written and verbal communication, Self-management of staff and the team.

















Experience

Software Developer

Full-time

Currently I am working as a senior developer for a company in Rosario, with international clients.

During the first months I worked for an internal company project. It was a platform where I could give courses for people internal to the company and thus train them, or, to give external courses to get new talent.

Participate from the discovery stage to the application maintenance stage.

We use TypeScript, ReactJs, NodeJs, and MongoDB. As a work methodology we use scrums with a transition from the maintenance stage to Kanban.

Period: Mar. 2023 - Currently

Company: Radium Rocket

🔘 Rosario, Santa Fe - Argentina

Software Developer

Part-time

In course 🛗

Feb 2022 - Apr 2022 🛗

I worked as a junior developer for a company in Rosario City. During that period I was in a project that consisted of creating a web application so that company employees can see the projects in which they participate, with their respective roles, rates, and hours worked. In addition to being able to perform tasks within the app.

The UI design was done with Figma, followed by some HTML layout and CSS styling. So all the user interaction was done through JavaScript. The whole server was also built to be able to list, create, edit, and delete managers and employees.

For the database, we use MongoDB, as it is a NoSQL database we had to make the relationships through extensions and tools that improve said DD.BB. such as Mongoose Schemas and Joi validations.

Period: Jan. 2021 - Feb. 2023 · 2 years 2 months

Company: FP Tech Solutions

Rosario, Santa Fe - Argentina

Education

⊘ UTN

Systems engineering

English	
⊖ Open English	In course 📆
Become a software developer	
	Aug 2022 - Dec 2022 :::
SQL Course	
○ Coderhouse	Oct 2022 - Dec 2022 🛗

React Js Course

○ Coderhouse	June 2022 - Aug 2022 📅
JavaScript Course	

○ Coderhouse

